<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pete Wilcox</title>
    <link>https://www.pcwilcox.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Pete Wilcox</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2020, Pete Wilcox.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 23:14:43 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pcwilcox.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Other</title>
      <link>https://www.pcwilcox.com/other/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 23:41:53 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.pcwilcox.com/other/</guid>
      <description>Outside of academia, I enjoy baseball, and am a devout fan of the Oakland Athletics. I am terrible at strategy games, but that doesn’t stop me from enjoying them. I also love long road trip vacations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://www.pcwilcox.com/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 23:41:50 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.pcwilcox.com/research/</guid>
      <description>My research interests are computer architecture, operating systems, and storage systems, with a focus on data center optimizations. Currently I am researching storage accelerator applications in computational genomics in collaboration with the UC Santa Cruz Genomics Institute.
For an interesting paper in this field I suggest:
 Y. Turakhia, G. Bejerano, and W. J. Dally, “Darwin: A Genomics Co-processor Provides up to 15,000X Acceleration on Long Read Assembly,” in Proceedings of the Twenty-Third International Conference on Architectural Support for Programming Languages and Operating Systems - ASPLOS ’18, Williamsburg, VA, USA, 2018, pp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>https://www.pcwilcox.com/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 23:41:47 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.pcwilcox.com/cv/</guid>
      <description>Education  B.S. in Computer Science, University of California, Santa Cruz, 2019  Phi Beta Kappa, summa cum laude, Dean&amp;rsquo;s List   Ph.D. in Computer Engineering, University of California, Santa Cruz, 2025 (expected)  Work experience   Summer 2019: Kernel Engineering Intern
 TidalScale, Inc. Functional Hypervisor Testing: Designed and built a functional hypervisor test facility using a custom Linux kernel module and device driver. Model-Specific Register Support: Utilized hypervisor test mechanism to implement and verify emulation for model-specific registers in the TidalScale hyperkernel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving to Hugo</title>
      <link>https://www.pcwilcox.com/moving-to-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 23:14:43 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.pcwilcox.com/moving-to-hugo/</guid>
      <description>My original Jekyll-based site stopped working for some reason. Rather than try to figure out what was going on with it, I decided to try out some alternative site generators. I&amp;rsquo;d heard about Hugo a bit so I decided to give it a try. The other thing I&amp;rsquo;d been meaning to do is start posting about all the various tech things I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on, as well as interesting talks I&amp;rsquo;ve seen, papers I&amp;rsquo;ve read, and that sort of thing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
